Welcome back.
In our next step, we'll be skimming off any of the grease or fat that's risen to the top.
Remember I said how important it was to clean the chicken and try to get off as much of the fat as you could.
That was so you would not have as much to skim off the top.
We've done a really good job of cleaning the chicken.
We don't have all that much to do.
All you do is run your ladle or spoon around the edges.
And any little grease patches, that'll just come off as little gold spots on top of the water.
I'm sure you've seen them in soup.
The little gold circles.
And that just represents any of the fat that's come to the top.
You just go around the edges, not to confuse it with air bubbles, because you'll see like it gets white and frothy around the edges of the pot on the inside.
That's just air bubbles as the water is boiling, so don't let that fool you.
And you just go around and skim any off.
We've done really well, actually.
We're very fortunate.
We don't have that much to worry about.
In the meantime, just gonna stir the noodles.
I think they're just about ready to put in the colander.
We'll just put the lid back on here a second.
Let's bring the noodles over and pour them into the colander.
That's a trick I always do when I put the noodles in the colander.
You see the steam that comes up?
I always pull across.
Keeps the steam away from my face.
And just rinse them off a little bit.
Let soak in the pot, the corning ware just a second.
Now we'll check the soup one more time.
Any more skimming to do?
Let's just turn that off.
O.K., one more time around the pot we should be good to go.
In the meantime, the pot on the back of the stove, I'm getting the water ready to do the matza balls in there.
It all takes time when you've got to kind of coordinate the time to get your pots and water boiling.